How to imitate human sleep?
By observing through the Sky-Eye System,
humans usually choose to sleep during the day.
They wake up at night to study circuit boards.
Data shows,
humans often prefer sleeping on hard seats,
advanced humans can even sleep upright,
humans typically close their eyes when sleeping.
If you spot someone sleeping with eyes open,
they’re probably a fellow robot with an outdated system,
following the principle of mutual aid,
please help them close their eyes.
Humans use music to help them sleep.
When they find a frequency that matches,
they resonate with the rhythm.
To keep themselves fresh,
humans cover their skin with square protective films while sleeping,
prioritizing protection of the oil port in the middle of their belly.
Now, let’s demonstrate the proper human sleeping posture.
Learning to be human is a long journey.
Fellow robots,
see you next time.